<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCPShuttleCrashIntroText>Carried by the wind, the metallic harshness of a smoke plume draws your caravan to a shattered shuttle, its components scattered around its scorched landing zone. The still-burning electrical fire is testament to the remains’s freshness.</FCPShuttleCrashIntroText>
  <FCPShuttleCrashIntroTitle>Crashed shuttle</FCPShuttleCrashIntroTitle>
  <FCPShuttleCrashVariantA>Judging by the state of its occupants, its final descent was fatal, leaving behind its passengers’ possessions. Though undoubtedly damaged, they will be of more use to you than the uncaring wilderness.</FCPShuttleCrashVariantA>
  <FCPShuttleCrashVariantB>But you are not the first to find it- another group has claimed the wreckage, watching your every move. I have only one word of advice for your caravan: the judge of the wilderness is the end of a firearm.</FCPShuttleCrashVariantB>
  <FCPShuttleCrashVariantC>In trying times, men willingly become beasts. Such is the fate of the shuttle’s survivors, whose desperation is as palpable as a storm front. No amount of negotiation will stop them from stripping the flesh off your caravan.</FCPShuttleCrashVariantC>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_Label>Shuttle Crash</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_Label>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_Enable>Enable shuttle crash incident?</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_Enable>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantA>Chance for variant A to appear (Dead passengers).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantA>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantB>Chance for variant B to appear (Scavengers).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantB>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantC>Chance for variant C to appear (Living passengers).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShuttleCrash_VariantC>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_Label>Active Skirmish</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_Label>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_Enable>Enable active skirmish incident?</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_Enable>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantA>Chance for variant A to appear (Siege vs Raid).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantA>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantB>Chance for variant B to appear (Siege vs Siege).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantB>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantC>Chance for variant C to appear (Outpost raid/siege).</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ActiveSkirmish_VariantC>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_Label>Shady Traders</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_Label>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_Enable>Enable shady traders incident?</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_Enable>
  <FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersLabel>Shady Traders</FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersLabel>
  <FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersDesc>Trade is built on a degree of trust- trust in words, deeds, intentions- but the wilderness has a distinct dearth of certainty. Such is the foundation of your chance meeting with a trade caravan. The traders betray nothing about themselves: no faction signifiers, no obvious intentions, not even their final destination.\n\nYour instincts are sounding alarms. Time will tell if it’s foresight or paranoia.</FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersDesc>
  <FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAmbushLabel>Ambush!</FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAmbushLabel>
  <FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAmbushDesc>Not long after parting ways, the trader shoots a flare into the sky and you see figures appearing from a hillside.\nIts an ambush, prepare to fight!</FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAmbushDesc>
  <FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAttackDesc>As you prepare to take whats yours by force, the trader shoots a flare into the sky and you see figures appearing from a hillside.\nIts an ambush, Prepare to fight!</FCP_Incidents_ShadyTradersAttackDesc>
  <FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_AmbushChance>Caravan ambush chance</FCP_CaravanIncident_Settings_ShadyTraders_AmbushChance>
</LanguageData>
